[
  {"question"  : "A",
   "answer"    :["c1","inter"],
   "id"        : 0 
  },
  {"question"  : "B",
   "answer"    :["c2","inter"],
   "id"        : 1
  },
  {"question"  :"A AND B",
   "answer"    : ["inter"],
   "id"        : 2  
  },
  {"question"  : "A NOT B",
   "answer"    :["c1"],
   "id"        : 3 
  },
  {"question"  : "B NOT A",
   "answer"    : ["c2"],
   "id"        : 4
  },
  {"question"  : "A OR B",
   "answer"    :["c1","c2","inter"],
   "id"        : 5 
  },
  {"question"  : "NOT B",
   "answer"    :["c1","uni"],
   "id"        : 6 
  },
  {"question"  : "NOT A",
   "answer"    : ["c2","uni"],
   "id"        : 7
  },
  {"question"  : "TRUE",
   "answer"    : ["c1","c2","inter","uni"],
   "id"        : 8
  },
  {"question"  : "Well Done!! Go to the next level...",
   "answer"    : [""],
   "id"        : 9
  }
]
